Bruno Criado

Pederneiras, SP, Brazil brunocriado@gmail.com Phone: 55 14 98136 8331

Summary

Graduate in Information Security with more than 12 years experience in IT infrastructure and software development, looking for new challenges and opportunities that allow him to learn new technologies share skills and work with new people.

Education

Catholic University of Brasilia, Diploma in Information Security

Industry Experience

Infrastructure Developer

Nov 2015 - Present

Flugel.it - https://www.flugel.it

Main Technologies: AWS, Python, terraform, ansible, ELK Stack, DevOps Tools, Docker

Responsibilities:

- Automating and implementing solutions using script languages and DevOps Tools
- Creating and developing system to aggregate value to client products
- Delivering Infrastructure

Software Engineer

Sep 2012 - Aug 2015

MStech - http://www.mstech.com.br

Main Technologies: Linux, Python, C/C++, Virtualization.

Responsibilities:

- Maintain a multi-platform solution for remote boot and hard disk protection on storage virtualization
- Maintaining a Linux distribution for hard drive imaging purpose
- Developing products for managing classrooms

Senior IT Infrastructure Analyst

May 2011 - Jul 2012

Fidelity Information Service - https://www.fisglobal.com

IT Infrastructure Analyst

Jan 2010 - Apr 2011

Eprom - http://www.eprom.com.br

IT Infrastructure Analyst

Mar 2009 - Dec 2009

Inforeason - http://www.inforeason.com.br

IT Infrastructure Analyst

Aug 2008 - Mar 2009

Lecom - http://www.lecom.com.br

IT Infrastructure Analyst

Mar 2007 - Aug 2008

Inforeason - http://www.inforeason.com.br

IT Intern

Mar 2004 - Aug 2005

Neobiz

Teaching Professor
Experience Senac - IT Technical College http://sp.senac.br/bauru

Sep 2009 - Apr 2011

Sep 2006 - Apr 2008

Senac - IT Technical College http://sp.senac.br/jau

Skills Base Programming Languages: C, Python

Professor

Configuration Management Tools: Ansible, saltstack

 $Orchestration/Provisioning\ Tools$: Terraform, SaltStack

Container Tools: Docker, Docker Swarm, Registry

Virtualization: VirtualBox/vagrant, qemu/KVM, VMWare, libvirt, libguestfs, LXC

Cloud: AWS, Digital Ocean, OpenStack

Monitoring: ELK Stack, Grafana, Prometheus, CloudWatch, Sensu

More Info

• Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/in/brunocriado

 $\bullet \ \, \mathbf{Github} \colon \texttt{https://github.com/dropped} \\$